Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173; Mustafa, Hossam Dine; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Fugitive From Life, 1965; ref173_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 29)
- In The Name of Love, 1965; ref174; Ziyada, Sayed; 1 Photographic Prints
  - In The Name of Love, 1965; ref174_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - In The Name of Love, 1965; ref174_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Lost Days, 1965; ref175; Sharaf, Bahaa Din; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Lost Days, 1965; ref175_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176; 4671; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176_000001; 4685; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176_000002; 4686; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176_000003; 4687; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176_000004; 4688; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Silence of the Storm, 1965; ref176_000005; 4689; Diaa Dine, Ahmed; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 44)
- The Confession, 1965; ref177; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Confession, 1965; ref177_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - The Confession, 1965; ref177_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - The Confession, 1965; ref177_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - The Confession, 1965; ref177_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - The Confession, 1965; ref177_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 49)
- The Mountain, 1965; ref178; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - The Mountain, 1965; ref178_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 30, Folder 59)
- The Sin, 1965; ref179; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000021; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000022; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000023; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000024; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000025; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000026; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000027; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000028; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000029; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000030; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000031; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000032; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000033; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000034; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000035; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000036; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000037; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000038; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000039; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000040; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000041; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000042; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000043; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000044; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000045; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000046; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000047; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000048; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000049; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000050; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000051; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000052; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000053; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000054; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000055; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000056; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000057; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000058; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000059; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000060; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000061; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000062; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000063; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000064; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - The Sin, 1965; ref179_000065; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 65)
- The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180; Mahmoud Farid; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 77)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - The Trouble-Makers, 1965; ref180_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 80)
- Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 86)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 87)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 88)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 89)
  - Widow and Three Daughters, 1965; ref181_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 31, Folder 90)
- Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Life Is Sweet, 1966; ref182_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Love in August, 1966; ref183; Saifi, Hassan; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Love in August, 1966; ref183_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 25)
- The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 Photographic Prints
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - The Enemy of Women, 1966; ref184_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Wedding Night, 1966; ref185; Barakat, Henry; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Wedding Night, 1966; ref185_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186; Hassan Reda; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Whom Do I Love, 1966; ref186_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 56)
- 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - 30 Days In Jail, 1966; ref187_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 61)
- Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Beggars' Strike, 1967; ref188_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 32, Folder 73)
- Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189; Mustafa, Hossam Dine; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Crime in a Quiet Neighborhood, 1967; ref189_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Love Holiday, 1967; ref190; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Love Holiday, 1967; ref190_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Love Holiday, 1967; ref190_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Love Holiday, 1967; ref190_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Love Holiday, 1967; ref190_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Nawara, 1967; ref191; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000012; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000013; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000014; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000015; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000016; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000017; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000018; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000019; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Nawara, 1967; ref191_000020; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Really Crazy Youth, 1967; ref192; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 Photographic Prints
  - Really Crazy Youth, 1967; ref192_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Really Crazy Youth, 1967; ref192_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Really Crazy Youth, 1967; ref192_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Really Crazy Youth, 1967; ref192_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; 94 x 145 cm (Box 33, Folder 38)